<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://github.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/blob/ship-log/NewHorizons/dialogue_schema.xsd">
    <NameField>Slate</NameField>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Start</Name>
        <EntryCondition>DEFAULT</EntryCondition>
		<SetPersistentCondition>COMPLETED_SLATE_EXPO</SetPersistentCondition>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Oh, and do be careful in this foggy weather...</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Yeah, did the forecast call for GIANT ANGLERFISH?!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Expo1</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>


	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Expo1</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Hey, chill out, Hatchling. You'll be fine. Besides, don't the fishies look kinda cute and cuddly? Hornfels seems kinda peeved about the whole thing, though... Maybe they'll share your teen hatchling angst!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Good, cuz I sure hope SOMEBODY around here has some reason!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Expo2a</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Yeah, I guess goliath predatory space-fish can be pretty cute, huh?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Expo2b</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Expo2a</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>C'mon now... You and I both know that "reason" is WAY overrated.</Page>
			<Page>Almost as overrated as that one song Gabbro is working on... "Cosmonaut in the Ocean" or something like that? Giant's Deep deserves a better anthem than that!</Page>
			<Page>Anyways, best of luck out there!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Expo2b</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>I know, right! Wait a second... You're never this agreeable! Say, you haven't been around any sap wine, have you?</Page>
			<Page>I dunno, sounds like I'll have to break out my Fit-to-Fly™ sobriety test...</Page>
			<Page>Question One: "If you were to have a flying, man-eating anglerfish as a pet, which of the following would be the best name for it?"</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>A. Geswaldo</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Expo3a</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>B. Jammer</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Expo3b</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>C. Ernesto</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Expo3c</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Expo3a</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Hmm... Says here that's the best name for a Jellyfish, not an Angler.</Page>
			<Page>Eh, close enough. Best of luck out there, Hatchling!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Expo3b</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Nope. No way. Welp, sounds like I'm gonna have to ground ya...</Page>
			<Page>Because that's definitely within my authority. Yessir.</Page>
			<Page>Ah, who am I kidding... Just... make sure you don't press the eject button on accident, okay? I don't wanna have to replace it.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Expo3c</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Yup! Looks like my expertly hand-crafted test is doing its job. What can I say, I'm just too brilliant. Good luck up there!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>
</DialogueTree>